把生日蜡烛准备好 因为...
Get the birthday candle ready, 'cause...
栗宝的胡萝卜蛋糕要登场啦
here comes Chestnut's carrot cake!
我知道要给他庆祝这特别的日子
I know we want this to be special,
但栗宝是只马
but Chestnut is a horse.
每个他没被做成宜家肉丸的日子
Any day he's not being made into an Ikea meatball
都是过生日
is a birthday.
记得 虽然今年是他十岁生日
And remember, even though it's his tenth birthday,
但得假装是六岁生日哦
we have to pretend he's six
不然他一整周都会很不爽的
or he'll be in a bad mood all week.
惊喜
Surprise!
栗宝生日快乐
Happy birthday, Chestnut!
麦克斯 蜡烛应该是他来吹
Max! He was supposed to do that!
有啥关系 我知道他的愿望
What? I know what he wished for.
有一天 我们能生活在一个
That one day, he and I live in a world
我们的爱能获得认同
where our love is recognized
并像其他同性恋夫妻享受同等权利的世界
and we have the same rights as gay couples.
快吃吧 宝贝
There you go, baby.
你看 他的鞋掉了
Hey, look, his shoe just fell off.
有可能是他踢掉鞋子
Or maybe he kicked it off
准备好来一场疯狂派对啦
'cause he's getting ready to partay.
这可怎么办啊
What are we gonna do?
我们没有钱了
We don't have any money.
我上周想要做按摩
I wanted a massage last week,
所以我坐公车时 就坐在一个
so I just sat next to someone on the bus
看起来会乱摸我的人旁边
who looked like he'd touch me.
我可能办法帮他换新鞋
I may have an idea how we can get 'em.
我在慕尼黑啤酒节钓的男人是个铁匠
A guy I picked up at Oktoberfest is a blacksmith.
我认为他是啦
At least I think he was.
我记得有皮围裙
I remember a leather apron
然后有个烧红的"铁棒"之类的
and something being heated in a fire.
我找到那个铁匠啦
Well, I found my blacksmith.
他现在跟用蜜蜂做衣服的
He now shares an artisan barn
一个女人合开一家工匠铺
with a lady who makes clothing out of bees.
现在我知道为什么我们小蛋糕店倒闭了
I guess that's why our cupcake shop didn't work.
我们没有提供大众"需要"的服务
We weren't providing a service that everyone needs.
我看了看栗宝
I looked at our boy,
他不只需要新的四只鞋子
and not only does Chestnut need four new shoes,
他还有香港蹄
He has a hoof fungus.
香港蹄 好贫民区风啊
A hoof fungus? That's so ghetto.
我很确定是我害的
I'm pretty sure he got it from me
我们一起洗澡时传染的吧
because we shower together.
新马蹄加兽医费用总计要一千四
And the cost of new shoes and vet fee? $1,400.
麦克斯 我好惭愧
Max, I feel awful.
我是个坏母亲
I'm a bad mother.
你才不是呢
You're not a bad mother.
我是坏母亲生出来的 所以我特了解
I know bad mothers. I came out of one.
姑娘们 那边是怎么回事
Ladies, what's happening over there?
我一看到有超过两个白人在一起
You know a gathering of more than two white people
我就心惊肉跳
makes me nervous.
厄尔 其中一个是亚洲人啊
Earl, one of them's asian.
都一样啦
Ah, same thing.
这餐厅谁是管事的
Who would I talk to about the diner?
我们有兴趣想租下这地方
We're interested in renting this location
来拍电视剧
to film a TV show.
我们觉得这餐厅超适合当杀人现场
We think your diner would be a great place to kill someone.
我懂
I get it.
每次走进这餐厅 我内心都死去一部分
'Cause every time I come in here, I die a little.
这是我的名片
Here's my card.
汤姆·吴 《法律与秩序 特殊受害者》剧组
Tom Woo, Law & Order: Special Victims Unit.
我勒个去 汤姆·吴
Shut your face, Tom Woo!
我爱死这剧了 尤其是《特殊受害者》系列
I love all the Law & Orders, especially SVU.
因为故事都是从新闻头条翻拍的
Their stories are ripped from the headlines,
我这人从不看报纸
and I don't read the newspaper,
所以你们就是我的新闻台啊
so that's where I get all my news.
很好 我去叫导演
Cool. Let me go get the director.
就是那边那位
That's him over there.
你看那导演多可爱
Look how cute the director is.
他符合我的粗犷男型呢
He's my rugged guy type.
也不是真粗汉子
Not really rugged at all,
只是从萨克斯第五大道精品百货里
but buys expensive, ruggedlooking clothing
买粗犷型名贵衣服的男人
from Saks 5th Avenue.
你好 我是迪杰·金斯利
Hi. DJ Kingsley.
胡子挺帅
Nice beard.
是自己长的呢
You grow out that stubble
还是把剃须刀设置到"霸气男星"模式了
or just set your razor to "Jason Statham."
打扰一下 先生
Excuse me, sir.
你的相貌很出色
You've got a great face.
您有当临演的经验吗
Have you ever done any extra work?
我出演过1973年经典电影
Well, I was in the 1973 classic
《尖叫吧 博古拉》
Scream, blacula, scream.
女主演在电影中踹了我蛋蛋
Pam grier kicked me in the nuts
然后骂我是"装逼男"
and called me a "jive turkey."
希望您愿意考虑一下
If you'd consider it,
我很乐意看到这集里有您出现
I'd love to have your look in the episode.
那我呢
Hey, what about me?
你可以要我剃光头 拖我到车后
You can shave my head, drag me behind a car,
或做任何我让人免费做过的事
or anything else I've already done for free.
没问题 而你想必是个女演员吧
Sure. And you must be an actress.
你太美 不可能只是个服务员
You're way too pretty to just be a waitress.
谢谢夸奖
Thank you!
其实我是有过一点表演经验啦
In fact I have done a little acting.
高中的时候 我扮演过《悲惨世界》里的芳汀
In high school, I portrayed Fantine in Les Miserables.
听你那么念就让我觉得好"悲催"了
Just hearing you say that makes me "Miserobble."
怎么样呢
Well, how about it?
想跟我一起玩
You wanna hang with me
然后在《特殊受害人》里当临演吗
and be an extra on Special Victims Unit?
付你112块一天
It pays 112 a day
再加上你每天应挣得的小费
plus whatever you normally make in tips.
那就是112加3块 我愿意
Oh, so about 115? I'm in.
老娘要买新的"马鞋"啦
Mama needs a new pair of horseshoes.
那你们的话事人呢
So where's the boss?
我就是话事人 但我去叫这地方的店主来吧
I'm the boss, but I'll get the guy who owns the place.
奥列格
Oleg!
他们要在这里拍电视剧
They're shooting a TV show here,
我的后脑勺或者我的侧乳
And the back of my head or the side of my boob
会入镜呢
is gonna be in it!
恭喜你啊 麦克斯
Good for you, Max.
我曾经上过乌克兰版《老大哥》
I was on Ukraine's version of big brother once,
其实就是乌克兰的每日生活
better known as just living in Ukraine.
阿憨 《法律与秩序 特殊受害人》
Han! Law and order: Special Victims Unit
想来餐厅里拍摄 如果你不同意
wants to shoot in the diner, and if you don't say yes,
我就会剁了你的"特殊受害鸡"
you'll be my special victim when I cut your unit off.
求你答应了 阿憨
Please say yes, Han.
我们当当背景路人甲就有钱拿呢
They're gonna pay us to be in the background.
但你们会演戏吗
But do you know how to act?
我们还真会呢
Actually we do.
我懂"方法演技" 她懂"冰毒演技"[音似]
My acting's method, whereas hers is more meth head.
进来吧
Hey, come in.
记得
And remember,
如果他拒绝 完全是口是心非
if he says no, he doesn't mean it.
他只是希望你能多挑逗挑逗他
He just wants you to flirt with him a little bit.
话别说太早 麦克斯
Not so fast, Max.
我是李憨 这家点的老板与产权所有人
Hello, I'm Han Lee, the owner and proprietor.
还"产权所有人"呢
Oh, "proprietor."
这五个字写起来比你身长还长[词深度]
That's word's bigger than you are.
你想要多少补偿费用
What kinda compensation do you want?
哎哟 我的亚洲兄弟
Whoa, whoa, my asian brother.
别这么直接 咱们慢慢来嘛
Slow down! Let's enjoy the dance.
我们想在这里拍摄
We'd like to shoot here.
这里的街头与骚气挺合适的
It's got the right amount of funk and skank.
如果我们演得够好 出衍生剧
If we do real good in this and get a spinoff,
这就会是我们的剧名了吧
that'll be the name of our show
"街妹与骚妹"
Funk and skank.
好吧 但我不想当骚妹
Okay, but I don't wanna be skank.
绝对是姐当骚妹好吗
Oh, clearly I'm skank.
我想说 我很荣幸
And may I say I'm honored
能跟你这与我旗鼓相当的对手切磋生意
I have such a worthy opponent to barter with.
我是加州帕萨迪纳市长大的
Dude, I'm from Pasadena.
我真不敢相信
I can't believe this!
我没想过有一天我能上到一个
I never thought I'd be in a TV show
并没有一堆人喊着
where no one was yelling,
"你不是她亲爹"的电视节目
"You are not the father!"
来吧 叫服务员临演出来
Let's go. Bring in the waitress extras.
我好喜欢这制服啊
Ooh, I love these uniforms!
感觉像《飞越比佛利》里的布兰达
I feel like Brenda from 90210
在核桃餐厅里打扮成50年代女服务员的样子
when she was dressed as that '50s waitress at the Peach Pit.
等我们成为巨星"街妹与骚妹"的时候
Well, when we're the big stars of funk and skank,
我们就不用穿任何制服了
we won't have to wear any uniforms.
等等 "街妹与骚妹"不是警察吗
But wait, aren't funk and skank cops?
不是 她们是妓女
Uh, no, they're hookers.
折衷一下吧
How about a compromise?
白天是警察 晚上是妓女如何
Cops by day, prostitutes by night?
所谓的警妓合一嘛
You know, copstitutes.
反正这俩行当 我们都是纽约最强的
Either way, we're New York's finest.
好了 大家准备 开始吧
Okay, everybody, ready! Here we go.
你看厄尔
Look at Earl over there.
厄尔 祝你好运
Good luck, Earl!
镜头对准门口 第八幕 第一次拍摄
Camera on the door. Scene eight, take one.
开拍 杀手走进来
And action! Shooter comes in.
结束 很好 复位
And cut! Good! Reset.
厄尔 太激励人心了
Earl, that was inspiring.
希望大家看完后 都能对罪案袖手旁观
I hope everyone who sees you goes out and ignores a crime.
刚才那一幕 感觉你这收银员才是主角
It was like that scene was about the cash register guy.
你为这幕戏带来更多内涵
You really brought something extra.
我有闻到艾美奖的味道哦
I smell an Emmy.
纯粹是大麻味而已
Oh, that's weed.
抱歉 让你们等着我们拍摄了
Hi. Sorry we haven't gotten to you guys yet.
你们何不去办公室里休息呢
Why don't you hang out in the office?
听说里面准备了上好寿司呢
I hear there's good sushi.
你看起来好漂亮
You look pretty.
导演好像对我有意思呢
I think the director kinda likes me.
心我不知道 但他的鸡鸡肯定对你有意思
Well, I don't know about him, but his penis does.
好了 镜头对准门口
Okay, camera on the door.
第八幕 第二次拍摄
Scene eight, take two.
开拍 杀手进门
And action! Shooter comes in.
呯 呯
Bang! Bang!
停
Cut!
抱歉 你是怎么进来的
Excuse me, how did you get through?
拜托
Oh, please.
柏林墙老娘都翻过来了
I once got through the Berlin wall.
两个拿着无线对讲机的娃能挡得住我吗
You think two kids with walkietalkies can stop me?
哇靠 这里面也太爽了吧
Damn, this room's got a sweet spread.
免费寿司 必须来
Free sushi? Uh, yes.
免费点心 废话吗
Free dessert? Uh duh.
这样太棒了
This is great.
我们得好好想想怎么才能
We've gotta figure out a way to get paid
多多免费蹭吃 坐着休息 还啥都不干
to sit around, eat free food, and do nothing more often.
这方面你早已是多年老手了吧
Oh, I think you cracked that code a long time ago.
如果我把寿司
Would it be tacky
都藏到我包里留着晚点吃 会丢人吗
if I packed some sushi in my purse for later?
我早把你那份和我那份藏好了
Already packed mine, already packed yours.
这里就是贵宾休息室
This is the VIP lounge.
你看 虾子的纱线都被处理过了呢
See? The shrimp have already been deturded.
你们在啊 姑娘们
Oh, hi, girls.
你们终于有新制服了 看起来好蠢啊
You finally got new uniforms. You look stupid.
我们这身制服可是由人家《法律与秩序》剧组
These are actually from the costume department
服装部门所准备的呢
of a little show called Law & Order: SVU
我跟麦克斯在里面客串演出哦
that Max and I are costarring in.
还客串呢 宝贝
Costars? Honey, please.
你们俩就临演而已
You two are just extras.
额外酬劳[临演] 外加满包的寿司
Um, extra paid and full of purse sushi.
准备好等你们上场了
They're ready for you two.
马上到
Oh! Be right there.
我去把包包放冰箱里就来
Just gonna put my purse in the fridge.
汤玛斯 汤姆 汤哥 能聊两句吗
Thomas. Tom. Tpain. Can we chat?
怎么了 兄弟
What is it, dude?
你们团队的人把酱油撒到我电脑上了
Your crew got soy sauce all over my computer.
根据我们的协议 你得赔偿所有的损失
And according to our agreement, you must pay all the damages.
-你要多少钱 -三百块
- How much do you want? - $300.
这就一台垃圾电脑
It's a piece of crap.
这电脑是我爸送我的呢
But it was a gift from my father.
我们的文化里 家人的地位你又不是不懂
And you know how important family is in our culture.
我真不知道 我被一对白人拉拉抚养长大
Again, I don't. I was raised by two white women.
我想当女主演该跟谁谈呢
Yes, uh, who do I talk to about becoming a star?
好兴奋啊
This is so exciting!
天啊 那女的一直把我的头往下按
God! That woman keeps pushing my head down.
就像是我平时的约会对象似的
I feel like I'm on a date with her.
你们俩就待在柜台后
Okay, so you guys are here behind the counter,
忙服务员的活儿
doing your waitress thing.
杀手枪口对准厨师
Shooter aims for the cook
结果误击到她 也就是女配角
but hits her, our featured waitress.
我是不是在这个剧里看过你了
Hey, didn't I already see you on SVU?
我想起来啦
Oh, yeah, I remember.
他们在哈德逊河里的小冰箱里找到你的头
They found your head in a mini fridge in the Hudson.
我就知道我见过你
I knew I recognized you.
等等 你在剧里死过了吗
Wait, we've already killed you?
抱歉 你不能演了
Sorry, babe, you're out.
你头部的那镜头很不错呢
Well, you gave great head.
汤姆 我们得找另一个人来演女配角
Tom, we gotta bump someone up to the featured waitress.
女配酬劳多一千块呢
Pays 1,000 more bucks.
麦克斯 那多出来的酬劳
Max, that could be the extra money
可以给栗宝治病呢
we need for Chestnut.
能让我们其中一个当吗
Could one of us do it?
你们俩有人会演中弹的样子吗
Can either of you act like you've been hit with a bullet?
真是无巧不成书
Well, it just so happens
小女子还真中弹过两次
I have been hit by a bullet twice
一次是在一家便利店 而另一次是在
Once at a 7-eleven and once running away
那家便利店的停车场里中的
in the parking lot of a 7-eleven.
所以这肯定是没问题
So yeah, I think I got this.
我觉得金发女孩比较适合这个角色
I'm thinking maybe a blonde would be better.
卡洛琳
Caroline?
我以前演到芳汀死亡的时候
Well, I did have a pretty convincing death scene
还颇为逼真的呢
as Fantine, and I died like...
要不我演给你看吧
Well, should I just show you?
你真是呆爆了
You are such a nerd.
挺好的 卡洛琳
That's great, Caroline.
特效组
Special effects,
帮卡洛琳装上爆血装置
put the blood device on Caroline.
她将是我们的"特殊受害者"
She's our special victim.
真的吗 由我演吗
Really? I got it?
是的 但记得少一点"法国大革命"元素
Yes, but a little less "French revolution,"
多一点"乖乖脸朝下当尸体"元素
and a lot more "face down on the floor."
你哪能演中弹啊 你连灌烈酒都不行[同词]
You can't take a shot. You can't even do a shot.
不要羡慕嫉妒恨好吗 我是为了栗宝
Don't be mad, Max. I'm doing this for Chestnut.
他喜欢我演死去的方式也不能怪我啊
And it's not my fault he liked my death scene.
他的小弟弟喜欢你的死戏才是真吧
He liked your death scene with his penis.
麦克斯 演艺事业把你丑恶的一面引出来了
Wow, Max, show business really brings out the worst in you.
你还没看到我参加婚宴时的样子
You haven't seen me at a wedding.
你就这么把手
Hello! You just put your hand
伸进女人的衣服 还连问都不问吗
down a woman's blouse without asking?
天天如此
Every day.
那需要我帮忙吗
Well, here. Can I help you?
不行 这是公会规定
No, it's a union thing.
你的手在里面有点久啊
Aren't you in there a little long?
马上 让我...
Yeah. Let me just...
卡洛琳 你身上的特技效果装置
Caroline, that special effects rig you're wearing
非常敏感
is very sensitive,
-所以别让任何东西靠近你的胸部 -除了我
- So don't let anything near your chest. - Except me.
别紧张
And don't be nervous.
你一定会非常上镜的 闪闪惹人爱
The camera's gonna love you. How could it not?
讨厌 别老跟人家调情啦
Dj, stop flirting with me.
我很快就会死掉 你永远都会忘不掉我的
I'm gonna die soon and you'll never get over me.
答应我你很快就会死掉
Promise you'll die soon?
麦克斯 我等下会被人用枪打死
Max, I'm about to be shot,
我可不想死之前还跟你闹不合
and I can't die with bad blood between us.
我们没事啦 你在帮我圆梦 姐妹
We're good. You're living my dream, girl.
-要让我骄傲哦 -我会的
- Do me proud. - I will.
不 不要拥抱
No! Don't hug with it!
卡洛琳 你触发了装置
Caroline, you set the thing off.
-我们还没开拍呢 -不是吧
- We weren't rolling. - Really?
那太可惜了 我刚才演得超棒呢
That's too bad, because that was gold.
先停机吧 各位 明天再接着拍
That's a wrap, everybody. We'll pick it up Tomorrow.
真的很抱歉 它自己就爆掉了
I'm so sorry. It just went off.
美女出差错很正常
Prettiest screwup all day.
你清理干净后
After you get cleaned up,
要不在我的酒店共进晚餐 如何
why don't we have dinner at my hotel?
吃饭吗 当然 乐意之至
Dinner? Yeah, I'd like that.
那就八点吧
Let's say 8:00.
我的助手会告诉你酒店地址和我的房号
My assistant will give you the address and my room number.
你现在跟我在梦里击毙你时
You know, this is exactly how you look in all my dreams
看起来一摸一样
where I shoot you.
那导演刚邀请我去他的酒店吃饭
The director just invited me to dinner at his hotel,
但是在他房间里吃
but it's in his room.
-你认为他是不是... -是的
- Do you think he... -Yes.
-所以他才... -没错
- Is that why he... -Yes.
-你会跟我一起去吗 -会
- Will you come with? - Yes.
或许你想错了
Maybe you're wrong.
或许他认为我的表演真的很...
Maybe he thought my audition was really...
不可能
No.
卡洛琳 或许下一次不要发挥得这么用力
Caroline, next time, maybe a little less.
记住
Now, remember.
如果导演在你的食物酒水里加了糖果状物
This director slips you anything that looks like a Sweet Tart,
那肯定就是迷奸药 会让你晕倒
it's probably that date rape drug that knocks you out
然后记忆混乱
and distorts your memory.
至少被我下药的男人都是这样的
Or at least that's what it does to the guys I give it to.
事情肯定不会发展到那地步
It's never gonna get to that.
我自己也有独家迷奸药
I have my own date rape drug.
我会滔滔不绝地谈论自己
I talk about myself incessantly
直到男人无聊到倒头大睡
till guys get bored and pass out.
如果这招不管用 那你的底线在哪里
So if that doesn't work, what are your limits?
是让人隔着毛衣摸 还是伸手进去摸
A little over the sweater, under sweater,
拜访下你的"前门" 还是走下你的"后门"
a little front door, back door,
还是爬爬你的"楼梯"
a little secret staircase?
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what that is,
但没人可以爬我的楼梯
but no one goes up my staircase,
即便是为了栗宝也不行
not even for Chestnut.
我最多就是给他亲两下
At the most, I'll do kissing.
你思考的方法就像个临演
You are thinking like an extra.
如果你想挣钱给栗宝买鞋子
You need to think like a star
去治疗 甚至是脱离科学神教
if you're gonna buy Chestnut shoes,
那你就得用主演的思考方式
then therapy, then a way out of Scientology.
你还找人陪你来了
Oh, hi. You brought company.
是啊 她是我的交通工具
Yes, she's my ride.
我们共用一张地铁卡
We share a subway card.
其实是她用地铁卡
Well, she uses the card.
我跳过验票闸门 然后她假装边追我
I jump the turnstile and she pretends to chase me,
边大喊"别担心 我会抓住她"
yelling "don't worry, I'll get her!"
进来吧
Well, come on in.
喝杯香槟再走 麦克斯
Stay for a glass of champagne, Max.
别担心要自己一个人坐地铁回家
Oh, and don't worry about taking the subway home alone.
我的司机可以送你回去
My driver can take you.
我有点进退两难了
Now I'm torn.
因为我虽然很不想你被迫
Because as much as I don't want you
屈服于他的淫威之下
to have sex against your will,
但我真的很想坐着豪华轿车去买麦当劳
I do wanna roll up to the Mcdonald's in a limo.
不着急
There's no rush.
过来 我们坐下来聊聊
Come on, let's sit down and hang out.
你人真好 邀请我上来
It was really nice of you to invite me up here
吃一顿普通的工作便饭
to have a casual, workrelated dinner.
麦克斯坐这边 卡洛琳坐那边
Max there, Caroline there,
而我则坐中间
and me, well, here.
导演总是忍不住发号施令
Can't turn it off, still directing.
我超爱这个酒店
You know, I love this hotel.
我曾经来过一次这里
I came here once to do a photo shoot
为一篇名为"20岁以下的
for a "20 under 20:
青少年百万富翁"的专题报道拍照
Teen millionaires to watch" spread,
我记得当时我刚剪了头发
and I remember I had just gotten my haircut,
那可是个艰难的决定
which was a big decision,
因为大家都知道我的招牌长发
'cause I was kinda known for my long hair.
而拍照那人希望我剪掉一英寸[不满3厘米]
And he wanted to take an inch off,
虽然听起来没什么大不了的
which doesn't sound like a big deal,
但当你的长发已经是你的招牌时...
but when you're known for your long hair...
人们就会希望看见你时 你的头发是长的
People are expecting to see you with long hair.
这样没事吧
So was that okay?
当然没事
Yeah, sure.
只是麦克斯也在
It-it's just Max is here,
我不想让她觉得备受冷落
and I don't want her to feel left out.
抱歉 我懂了
Sorry. Got it.
真不错
That was nice.
你的接吻技术真不错
You're a good kisser.
你在吃肉桂味的薄荷糖吗
Are you eating a cinnamon Altoid?
其实是我在吃
I'm eating a cinnamon Altoid.
那我间接一吻芳泽啦
Well, then I just tasted you.
迪杰 我想你可能误会了
Look, DJ, I think you have the wrong idea.
等我一下
Hold that thought.
如果是工作电话 这种时候我绝对不接
I would never interrupt this for a work call,
可惜是我老婆打来的 我想跟孩子们说晚安
but it's my wife and I wanna say "good night" to the kids.
那家伙是个玩咖
That guy's a player.
估计我没办法用说的来解决了
I'm not talking my way out of this one.
-我们完蛋了 -是啊
- We're screwed. - Yeah.
他的容忍力真是惊人
He's got a high tolerance.
你的"长发"大论差点把我弄昏睡了
Your longhair speech almost roofied me.
我们该怎么办 我可不想得罪他
What do we do, Max? I don't want to offend him.
我们需要临演的钱给栗宝买鞋
We need that extra money for Chestnut.
这活脱就像书里的老故事
This is the oldest tale in the book
女人为了给孩子买鞋 被迫出卖自己的肉体
a woman forced to trade her body to get her child shoes.
像莎士比亚和狄更斯的故事那样悲催
It's Shakespearian, it's Dickensian,
像卡戴珊那样卖肉
It's Kardashian.
往好的方面想
Look at the bright side.
你之前就觉得他很性感
You already thought he was sexy,
所以你可能最终还是会跟他上床
so you were probably gonna sleep with him eventually.
现在知道他是已婚人士
And now that he's married,
你就不用担心他会跟其他人偷情
you know he won't cheat on you with somebody else
因为你就是其他人
because you're that somebody else.
你就是那个小三
You a side bitch!
不行 麦克斯 我可以跟他说实话
No, Max, I can just tell him how I feel.
再说了 他可能已经理解了
Besides, he probably already got it.
你也听到我刚说他误会了
You heard me tell him he read the signs wrong.
显然他误以为是"3P马上就来"
Apparently the sign he read said "Threeway up ahead."
身材很棒吧
Pretty good, right?
要兼顾热门剧集 老婆 孩子
Hit show, wife, kids.
我居然还有时间去健身
Still find time to get to the gym.
在开始之前 你们俩需要多喝点酒吗
So you guys need to drink a little more before we do this?
我可是不用哦
'cause I don't.
好吧 在毛巾扯下来之前
All right, I'm just gonna say this
我有话要说
before that towel comes off.
我觉得你可能误会了我的意思
I think you've misread the signals here.
是吗 那真扫兴
Really! That sucks.
抱歉 这种事经常发生
I'm sorry. These things happen.
我想起来有一次我跟
It reminds me of that time I had tea
迪拜的王子喝茶 他就以为他买了我了
with that prince in Dubai and he thought he bought me.
结果他买的是另外一位金发妞
Turns out he bought a different blonde.
男人呀
Oh, men!
-早上好 迪杰 -早上好
- Good morning, DJ. - Morning!
瞧 麦克斯 没有芥蒂
See, Max? No hard feelings.
我说过不会有事的
I told you it was gonna work out.
我已经准备好安装我的爆血袋了
Hi! I'm ready for my fake blood pouch.
我觉得你可能塞错胸部了
Um, I think you got the wrong breasts.
虽然你人是个大老粗 但动作却很温柔嘛
But for a rough guy, you got a soft touch.
人员安排有改动
There's been a change.
现在麦克斯是女配角 而你是背演
Uh, Max is now getting featured, and you're in the B.G.
背景演员
Background.
-这是真材实料吗 -是的
- These are real? - Yep.
不错嘛
Nice job.
你听到了吗 麦克斯 现在我是背景演员
You hear that, Max? Now I'm in the B.G.
我没有上迪杰 所以就滚去背景
I didn't do DJ, so I'm in the B.G.
麦克斯
Max!
在午餐前 我们有时间实拍一次
We have time for one full take before lunch,
午餐后我们会回来 继续拍你那部分
then we'll come back and do the rest of your coverage after.
或许我们可以在我的休息拖车里
Hey, maybe you and I could have a little lunch together
共进午餐
in my trailer.
我确实很爱拖车
Well, I do love a trailer.
好的 各位 按计划执行
Okay, let's stay on schedule, people.
我的孩子在学校读诗歌呢
My kid's reading a poem at school.
对了 你的奶子看起来真棒
By the way, your rack looks fantastic.
你看起来真是个好爸爸
You seem like a great dad.
迪杰 是因为昨晚
DJ, is this about last night,
我不愿意只裹一条浴巾的关系吗
'cause I wouldn't wear a towel?
当然不是 我们没事
No. No, we're good.
我不想看到她 把她丢去最角落
I don't wanna see that. Bury her deep.
"把她丢去最角落"
"Bury her deep"?
他刚才是说"把她丢去最角落"吗
Did he just say, "bury her deep"?
卡洛琳 你得去那边工作
Caroline, you need to work back there.
好莱坞就这么对待女人的吗
Is this how Hollywood treats women?
好莱坞对每个人都这样
This is how Hollywood treats everyone.
各就各位
Everybody ready.
麦克斯 如果你这么做 你就等于在卖肉
Max, if you do this, you'll be getting paid for sex.
也是时候了
Well, it's about time.
各就各位
Places, everyone.
你不必这样做 栗宝是我的马
You don't have to do this. Chestnut is my horse.
开拍 麦克斯 你在擦桌子
And action! Max, you're wiping the counter.
杀手走了进来 你抬头看
The killer comes in. You look up.
别这样
Don't do it.
我们可以想别的法子挣钱
We can find money somewhere else.
停 汤姆 我不想看见她
Cut! Tom, I don't wanna see her.
-卡洛琳 -他们来了
- Caroline. - Here they come.
好了 各位 重新开始
Come on, everybody. Back to one.
开拍 麦克斯 你在擦桌子
And action! Max, you're wiping the counter.
杀手走了进来 你抬头看
The killer comes in. You look up.
上菜
Pick up!
麦克斯 真的 这不值得
Max, seriously, it's not worth it.
停 把她弄出去
Cut! Get her out of there.
重新调整下
Reset, reset.
各位 真是不好意思
Sorry about all that, people.
现在请赐给我那颗
Now, let's give me the bullet
我等了一生的子弹吧
I've been waiting for my whole life.
我很久没觉得自己这么不受人待见了
I haven't felt this unwanted since I tried to
上一次还是在我教贫民窟小孩织毛衣的时候
teach those innercity school kids how to knit.
卡洛琳 你得待在这里
Seriously, Caroline, you have to stay here,
远离镜头
away from the shot,
不然到最后你们谁都挣不着钱
or neither of you is gonna be paid.
汤姆 你知道戏里还缺点什么吗
Hey, Tom, you know what this scene needs?
收银员
A little more cashier.
那群剧组人员把餐厅糟蹋得乱七八糟
Oy, that crew is doing a lot of damage to this diner.
我现在在糟蹋这瓶高级纯净水
Well, I'm doing some damage to this fancy french water.
地板要赔150块 用掉的餐巾要付20块
150 for the floor, 20 for the napkins they used,
还有...
And...
那幅美丽的"城市掠影"要赔55块
And 55 bucks for that gorgeous picture of the city.
这真是太荒谬了
This is ridiculous.
我还要等多久才能被发掘
How much longer do I have to wait to be discovered?
像其他美国人那样
Do what every other American would do
无需苦干 只需把自己的性爱录像放上网就行
skip the hard work and put out a sex tape.
我要出去了 我的唇膏呢
No, I'm gonna go out there. Where's my lipstick?
来 帮拿下我的瘦身哑铃
Here, hold my shake weight.
还有我的饮料
And my Fresca.
你好
Oh, hi.
我要找谁才能参演这部戏
Who do I talk to about getting a part in this thing?
我已经让发饼干的人
I mean, I already let the guy
摸过我的胸部了
who puts out the cookies touch my boobs.
我们没有人负责发饼干
We don't have a guy who puts out cookies.
在这呢
Yo.
好了 各就各位 摄像机准备
Okay, everybody ready! Camera up!
-他看起来是号人物 -别过去
- Oh, he looks important. - Oh, no, no!
-站住 -不 放手
- Stop, stop! - No! Let go!
别按到血液袋爆破开关
Not the blood switch!
麦克斯中枪了
Someone shot Max!
停 汤姆 把麦克斯换掉
Cut! Tom, get rid of Max too.
再给我找个女演员
Get me another girl.
典型的臭男人
Typical!
往我胸部"射"完一发后 就立刻把我甩掉
Shoot on my chest and you're done with me.
你好 你是要找新的女演员吗
Hi, you looking for a new girl?
我上一次被搞成这样的时候
Last time I looked like this,
还是我从吸毒迷幻派对中醒来
I was coming out of an acid trip
我的朋友丹尼尔却不见了
and my friend Daniel was missing.
不得不承认
I gotta admit,
中枪会让人觉得自己是黑帮服务员
getting shot felt kinda gangsta waitress.
我就像个餐馆大姐头
I'm like notorious BLT.
事情是这样的
So here's the deal.
我们会付给你昨天的费用
We'll pay you for the day yesterday,
但不会付今天和女配角的费用
but not for today or for the featured extra.
-你说什么 -话别说太早 兄弟
- Say what? - Not so fast, my brother.
这是我餐厅损失的最新账单
Here is the latest tally for my diner damage.
最后那一千块钱是怎么回事
What's this last $1,000 charge?
那是给麦克斯和卡洛琳的精神损失费
That is for the damage done to Max and Caroline.
根据剧组传闻说
According to crew scuttlebutt,
导演昨晚试图搞一些不道德的潜规则
the director tried some funny business last night.
这样有点过分了吧 伙计
This is not cool, dude.
这当然很过分啦 朋友
It is most decidedly not cool, pal.
或许我可以跟工会的人
So maybe there is someone in a union I can talk to
说说这笔精神损失费
about this particular damage.
更不用说你跟阿憨共事
Not to mention the child labor laws you violated
违反了童工保护法
by working with Han.
别跟任何人说 我会叫他付钱的
Don't talk to anyone. I'll get 'em paid.
真气人
This sucks.
我就知道该去丹尼斯连锁西餐厅拍摄
I knew we should've shot at a Denny's.
阿憨 你刚为我们俩做的事
Han, that is the sweetest, coolest thing
-真是既贴心又帅气 -的确
- You just did for us. - It is,
今晚卡洛琳绝对会愿意跟你上床
and Caroline is totally gonna put out for you tonight.
反正现在卖肉是她的专长
That's kind of her thing now.
我不想任何人占你们俩的便宜
Well, I don't want anyone to take advantage of you two.
你们是我的姑娘
You're my girls.
在今晚《街妹与骚妹》的特别节目中
And tonight, on a very special episode of funk and skank,
那个可爱的亚洲小男人原来是这俩姑娘的皮条客
the cute, tiny Asian guy turns out to be the girls' pimp,
而警妓终于买得起马蹄铁啦
and the copstitutes are able to buy new horseshoes.